Billy Byers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Full Scores (Box 1-35)
  - [Notebook], Notebook which came with the collection, inventorying most of its contents. (Box 35)
Don’t bring Lulu Grey, Joel see Billy Rose medley
Don’t call me Mama anymore Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Don’t dream of anybody (but me) Page, Patti
Don’t fence me in Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Don’t rain on my parade Helmsley & Weeks see Hello Dolly insert
Don’t sleep in the subway Page, Patti
Don’t you feel my leg Gaynor, Mitzi
Donny & Marie ABC 25th anniversary
Donny hit medley The Osmonds
Doo dee doo Helmsley & Weeks
Dooh-wah-diddy Basie, Count
Down in the depths Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Down with love Reese, Della
Dr. Doolittle Bushkin, Joe
Dream a little dream of me Elliot, [Mama] Cass see Cass’ golden oldies
Drowsy eyes Brown Rice
Dusty’s bows Springfield, Dusty
Early morning blues and greens Raney, Sue
Easter parade Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Eatin’ out tonight American Express–79
Eighty mph thru beer can country Prowse, Juliet
Eldreb laughs Hamlisch, Marvin
Eleanor Rigby Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
Ellington medley (fix) Rawls, Lou
Embraceable you Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
End crawl... Calucci’s Dept. TV film
End title M.I.M. pilot
Enter laughing Carter, Mel
Ev’ry day of my life Vinton, Bobby see Hit medley ‘77
Everybody step Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Everybody’s doing it Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Everybody’s talking Graham, Virginia
Everyday that I may love McKuen, Rod
Everything old is new again Crosby, Bing
Everything old is new again Andrews, Julie
Extraordinary Elliot, [Mama] Cass
F. Ticket ballet pt II/part III Baryshnikov on Broadway
Fabulous places Bushkin, Joe
Falling ballad medley Heatherton, Joey
Family of man medley Rodgers/Hart tv special
Fanfare - What the world needs now Lewis, Jerry
Far from the home I love Zadora, Pia
Fascinatin’ rhythm Lane, Abbe see Opening ‘77
Fascinatin’ rhythm Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Fat and greasy Vereen, Ben see Fats Waller tribute
Fats Waller tribute Vereen, Ben
Feelin’ good Meeza, Lee
A fella with an umbrella Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Feudin’ & fightin’ Gaynor, Mitzi
Fifth of Beethoven Gaynor, Mitzi see Sugar blues
Final bows.... Grey, Joel
Finale Davis, Charles
Finale ‘75 new ending Heatherton, Joey
Fine and dandy - play off Diller, Phyllis
Fine and mellow Ross, Diana
A fine romance Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Fiore serenade McKuen, Rod
Fire and rain Carroll, Diahann
Five meanings of love Raney, Sue
A foggy day Sinatra, Frank
A foggy day Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr. see Y.M.C.A.
Foot and cymbal dance (opener) MacLaine, Shirley
Foot ballet Run America live tv ‘78
For once in my life Eckstine, Billy
For once in my life Raney, Sue
For once in my life Meeza, Lee
For once in my life Lewis, Jerry
For the first time Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
For the rest of my life Helmsley & Weeks
For you Reese, Della
Forty-second Street Rogers, Ginger
Forty-second Street Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Forty without fear McKuen, Rod
Foto montage Gaynor, Mitzi
Fred Noel, Dick
Frère Jacques Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
A friend - My friend McKuen, Rod
Frisco Basie, Count
The gal that got away Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Galveston Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Georgia boy Raney, Sue
Gershwin medley Andrews, Julie
Get me to the church on time Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Get ready Hope, Bob
Getaway Stevens, Connie
Getting to know you Raney, Sue see Know you opener
George M. Cohan medley Franchi, Sergio
The girl that I marry Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Give it all you got Boston Pops
Give me that old time religion McKuen, Rod see Religious medley ‘73
Give my regards to Broadway Franchi, Sergio see George M. Cohan medley
Give my regards to Broadway Newley, Anthony see Opening cont.
Give my regards to Broadway Reese, Della
Give my regards to Broadway The Music Scene
Give the baby a birthday kiss for us The Music Scene
Gizzoutas Run America live tv ‘78
Glow’s worms/Glow worm Glow, Bernie
Go away, little girl Steve and Eydie see They’re playing our song....
Go away little girl The Osmonds see Medley - Osmond Brothers
Go away little girl The Osmonds see Donny hit medley
God bless America Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Golden earrings Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot VI
Golden earrings Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot part II
Gone at last Three Girls Three
Gonna make you love me Falana, Lola
Good lovin’ I am...I said Carroll, Diahann
Good morning heartache Ross, Diana
Good nights/Always Steve and Eydie
Goodbye to violence TV Critics Awards 1977
Goodnight but not goodbye Star Wars
Goodnight, my someone Jones, Shirley see Music Man - medley
Goodnights b.g. Steve and Eydie
Got to get you into my life Ladd, Cheryl
Grand entrance —
Great balls of fire The Music Scene
Great day Grey, Joel see Billy Rose medley
The greatest love of all Run America live tv ‘78
The greatest love Uggams, Leslie
Groovin’ Raney, Sue
Group jump M.I.M. pilot
Guess I’d rather be in Colorado McKuen, Rod
Guys and dolls Baryshnikov on Broadway
Guys and dolls vocal tag, Intro Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
Half time Vereen, Ben
Hallelujah Radio City Music Hall Special
Hang up your hat Phil Feldman Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Happy birthday Las Vegas.... Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
Happy day Falana, Lola see Sweet Lord
Happy days ABC 25th anniversary see Welk-Lennon Sisters medley
Happy days are here again Apple Pie
Happy holidays Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Happy hour Honey & Sis
Happy is a boy McKuen, Rod see McKuen retrospective 73
Happy together Lane, Abbe
Hava nagila Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Have a little talk Uggams, Leslie see Smiling faces/Have a little talk
Have I stayed too long at the fair Raney, Sue
Have yourself a merry little Christmas Crosby, Bing see Christmas medley
Have yourself a merry little Christmas Ann-Margret
Have yourself a merry little Christmas Ann-Margret see Christmas 1973
He lied Raff, Reneé
He’s funny that way Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
He’s got the whole world in his hands Basie, Count
Heat wave Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
A heavy load Ann-Margret
Heliotrope bouquet Hamlisch, Marvin
Hello Dolly Helmsley & Weeks see Hello Dolly insert
Hello Dolly Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Hello Dolly Severinsen, Doc see Severinsen/Armstrong suite
Hello Dolly, finale Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
Hello Dolly insert Helmsley & Weeks
Hello young lovers Rodgers/Hart tv special see Family of man medley
Hello young lovers - opening Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy
Help Uggams, Leslie see This is your life - Help
Help me make it through the night Carroll, Diahann see Love number
Her face Hartman, David
Here comes Virginia Jules Chaiken, producer
Here I go again The Music Scene
Here’s that rainy day Hartman, David
Here’s that rainy day Sinatra, Nancy see Rain and sun medley
Hey girl The Osmonds see Donny hit medley
Hey jealous lover Basie, Count
Hichcock railway Cardinal, Vin
Higher and higher Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
Higher and higher Loring, Gloria
Higher and higher Vinton, Bobby
Hit medley ‘77 Vinton, Bobby
Holiday for strings Raney, Sue
Holly holly Diamond, Neil
Hollywood movie girls Ann-Margret
Homeward bound Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Honey’s telephone Hanna-Barbera
Honeysuckle Rose Vereen, Ben see Fats Waller tribute
Hooray for Captain Spaulding on and off The Music Scene
Hooray for Hollywood Rogers, Ginger
Hope Raney, Sue
Hospitality suite Reddy, Helen
Hound dog Jones, Tom see Something - Hound dog - Lola
House of the rising sun Meeza, Lee
How about me? Raney, Sue
How deep is the ocean? Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
How great thou art Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
How long has this been going on Ann-Margret see TV concert section
How long has this been going on Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Hucklebuck Basie, Count
Hurricane Sadie Ann-Margret
Hustle my bustle —
I am singing Three Girls Three
I begged her Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
I believe in music TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
I can do a trick Lovell, Marilyn
I can do that Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr. see This is the...
I can hear the music Raney, Sue
I can see clearly Minnelli, Liza
I can’t believe that you’re in love with me Reese, Della
I can’t give you anything but love Ann-Margret see Rio medley
I can’t remember ever loving you Raney, Sue
I can’t stop lovin’ you Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
I can’t stop loving you Reese, Della
I can’t take it Page, Patti
I can’t take my eyes off of you Page, Patti
I didn’t know what time it was The Supremes
I do what I please —
I don’t know why, I just do Ann-Margret see TV concert section
I don’t wanna go Stevens, Connie
I fall in love too easily Rowles, Stacey
I go to Rio Ann-Margret see Rio medley
I got it bad Rawls, Lou see Ellington medley (fix)
I got it bad and that ain’t good Vaughan, Sarah
I got lost in his arms Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
I got plenty of nothin’ Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
I got rhythm Steve and Eydie see Tra la la - symphony
I got rhythm Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
I got the sun in the morning Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
I gotta right to sing the blues Falana, Lola
I had a ball Reese, Della
I hadn’t anyone ‘till you Reese, Della
I happen to like New York Newley, Anthony see Opening cont.
I haven’t got anything better to do Page, Patti
I honestly love you TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
I just make believe you love me Zadora, Pia
I left my heart in San Francisco off The Music Scene
I let a song go out of my heart Vaughan, Sarah
I love a piano Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
I love a piano Hamlisch, Marvin
I love how you love me Vinton, Bobby see Hit medley ‘77
I love you Vaughan, Sarah see Sassy and Billy Eckstine
I miss you so Mateo, Pete and Beverly Layne/Layme
I poured my heart into a song Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
I remember you Lamour, Dorothy see South Sea medley
I still believe in love Steve and Eydie
I think I like you Bushkin, Joe
I wanna be a dancin’ man Vereen, Ben
I wanna listen to rag Minnelli, Liza
I wanna make the world laugh Davis, Charles see Opening
I want to be happy Adams, Edie
I want to be happy Gaynor, Mitzi see When you’re smiling
I want to go back to Michigan Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
I wish you love Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
I won’t dance —
I won’t last a day without you Andrews, Julie
I won’t last a day without you Crosby, Harry
I write the songs TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
I’ll be seeing you Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
I’ll be your baby tonight The Music Scene
I’ll begin again Nabors, Jim
I’ll get by Basie, Count
I’ll get by Raney, Sue
I’ll never fall in love again Jones, Tom
I’ll never miss her till I think of her Eckstine, Billy
I’ll never smile again Basie, Count
I’ll never smile again Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
I’ll never smile again Sinatra, Frank Jr.
I’ll never smile again Vinton, Bobby see Big band medley
I’ll remember you Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
I’ll say a prayer for you Steve and Eydie see They’re playing our song....
I’m a little bit country ABC 25th anniversary see Donny and Marie
I’m a tree Elliot, [Mama] Cass
I’m a Yankee-doodle dandy Franchi, Sergio see also George M. Cohan medley
I’m always chasing rainbows Hamill, Dorothy see Opening
I’m always chasing rainbows Adams, Edie
I’m an old cowhand Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
I’m comin’ home again Lucien, John
I’m coming home again Barnett, Eileen
I’m flying Sinatra, Nancy
I’m gonna sit right down and write.... Vereen, Ben see Fats Waller tribute
I’m just wild about Harry Three Girls Three see Wild medley
I’m looking over a four leaf clover Crosby, Bing see Everything old is new again
I’m not afraid Sinatra, Nancy
I’m saved McKuen, Rod see Religious medley ‘73
I’m so very happy Eckstine, Billy
I’ve got a crush on you Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
I’ve got a crush on you Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
I’ve got a lovely bunch of cocoanuts Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot IIII
I’ve got a lovely bunch of cocoanuts Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot II
I’ve got my love to keep me warm Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
I’ve got to be me Steve and Eydie see They’re playing our song....
I’ve got you under my skin Lucien, John
I’ve got your number Stevens, Connie
I’ve gotta be me Meeza, Lee
I’ve grown accustomed to her face bows Andrews, Julie
I’ve told every little star Reese, Della
If Springfield, Dusty
If McKuen, Rod
If he really knew Steve and Eydie
If I call you friend Stevens, Connie
If I lose this dream Jeffries, Fran
If I loved you Jones, Shirley
If I ruled the world Andrews, Julie
If she walked into my life (2) Eckstine, Billy
If you are but a dream Damone, Vic
If you were the only boy Reese, Della
Imagination Falana, Lola
In a mellow tone Vaughan, Sarah
In a sentimental mood Vaughan, Sarah
In the blue of the night Crosby, Bing
In the city Falana, Lola
In the interim Raff, Reneé
In the mood Vinton, Bobby see Big band medley
In the night McKuen, Rod
In the wee small hours of the morning Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
In the wee small hours of the morning Basie, Count
Indiana Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Iowa stubborn Jones, Shirley see Music Man - medley
Isn’t she lovely - sunshine medley Jeffries, Fran
Isn’t this a lovely day Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
It ain’t necessarily so Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
It could happen to you Lamour, Dorothy see South Sea medley
It don’t mean a thing Reese, Della
It don’t mean a thing if it ain’t got.... Vaughan, Sarah
It don’t mean a thing if it ain’t got that.... Vereen, Ben
It might as well be spring on/off Gaynor, Mitzi
It never entered my mind The Supremes
It was a good time Franchi, Sergio
It’s a lovely day today Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
It’s a man’s world O’Connor, Carroll
It’s a miracle ABC 25th anniversary
It’s a musical world Davis, Jr., Sammy
It’s all right with me The Music Scene
It’s easy to remember Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
It’s just a matter of time Raney, Sue
It’s not where you start Crosby, Bing
It’s one of those songs Ann-Margret see Show biz medley
It’s only a paper moon Grey, Joel see Billy Rose medley
It’s the same old shillelagh Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot V
It’s wild Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
Ivy Yarborough, Glenn
J.B. bows Byner, John
Jackson Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Jang pierewiet Raff, Reneé
Je t’attends Yarborough, Glenn
Jean The Music Scene
Jefferson’s rock Jeffersons
Jingle bells Crosby, Bing see Christmas medley
Johnny B. Goode Berry, Chuck
The joint is jumping Vereen, Ben
Josh and Kelley Josh and Kelley
June is busting out all over —
Just a gigolo Reese, Della
Just a little lovin’ Horne, Lena
Just say I love you too much Mateo, Pete and Beverly Layne/Layme
Kaleidescope Yarborough, Glenn
Kansas City Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Kiddie stars forever disco march ABC 25th anniversary
Know you opener Raney, Sue
Knowing when to leave Raney, Sue
Lady in red part Ann-Margret
Land of make believe Stevens, Connie
Last jump M.I.M. pilot
Lazy river The Osmonds
Lean on me Manhattans
The legend Stevens, Connie
Let it snow Reese, Della
Let it snow Crosby, Bing see Christmas medley
Let me be there TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
Let me down easy Raney, Sue
Let me sing and I’m happy Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Let me take you with me McKuen, Rod
Let the little girl dance The Osmonds
Let the water run down Cardinal, Vin
Let there be love Raff, Reneé
Let’s call the whole thing off Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Let’s do it.... Gaynor, Mitzi
Let’s take an old fashioned walk Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Life is a woman Stop the World I Want to Get Off
Life upon the wicked stage Ann-Margret see Show Boat sequence part II
Light my fire Reese, Della
Limehouse blues Gaynor, Mitzi
Limehouse, home of the blues —
Lisa Brite and Dark McKuen, Rod
Little boy lost Dickey, Joe
Little girl blue Ross, Diana see Rodgers and Hart medley
Little green apples Hartman, David
A little help from my friends Raney, Sue
Little woman The Music Scene
Live for life Raney, Sue
Living curtain - fanfare MGM Grand Hotel
Liza Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
Liza - Desi - opening Minnelli, Liza
London bridge special... Jones, Tom
Long and winding road combo Byner, John
The long slide Winding, Kai
The look of love The Music Scene
Louisiana woman Nabors, Jim
Lounging at the Waldorf Vereen, Ben see Fats Waller tribute
Love Reese, Della
Love (Webster’s definition) Raney, Sue
Love a lot part I (finale) new lead in Diller, Phyllis
Love American style ABC 25th anniversary see Welk-Lennon Sisters medley
Love and love alone Williams, Andy
Love conquers all McKuen, Rod
Love love song Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy
Love me tender Raney, Sue
Love me tonight Horne, Lena
Love number Carroll, Diahann
Love one another Nabors, Jim
Love story Falana, Lola see Academy 71 medley
Love story Goulet, Robert/Carol Lawrence
Love story Eden, Barbara
A love story Peters, Bernadette
Love will find a way Gaynor, Mitzi
Love will keep us together ABC 25th anniversary see Singers medley
Love you didn’t do right by me Peters, Bernadette
A lovely way to spend an evening Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Lover come back to me Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Luck be a lady.... Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
Lullaby of Broadway Newley, Anthony see Opening cont.
Lullaby of Broadway Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Lullaby of Broadway Bennett, Tony
Lullaby of Broadway Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Lush life Vaughan, Sarah
Lush life Reese, Della
M1-opening talk Ann-Margret
MacArthur Park Raney, Sue see Didn’t we medley
Mack the Knife Severinsen, Doc see Severinsen/Armstrong suite
Magic is the moonlight intro Minnelli, Liza
Magic time Diller, Phyllis
Main title Run America live tv ‘78
Make ‘em feel good Barnett, Eileen
Make believe Keel, Howard and [Kathryn] Grayson
Make someone happy Steve and Eydie
Make your own kind of music The Music Scene
Make your own kind of music Elliot, [Mama] Cass see Cass’ golden oldies
Make your own kind of music Streisand, Barbra see Sing - music
Making our dreams come true ABC 25th anniversary see Welk-Lennon Sisters medley
Mama undescore + crawl Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Mama’s party Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Mammy Lane, Abbe see Celebrity medley
The man I love Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
The man that got away Hamlisch, Marvin
Manchester McKuen, Rod
Mancini medley Andrews, Julie
Marie Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Marieke —
Marrying for love Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Mary Hartman —
Mary Tyler Moore [theme] TV Critics Awards 1977 see Miscellaneous cues
Mary zoo - play on - play off Diller, Phyllis
Mary’s a grand old name Franchi, Sergio see George M. Cohan medley
May the good lord bless and keep you Ford Special
Maybe this time Byner, John
Maybe this time (2) Eckstine, Billy
Maybellene The Music Scene
McKuen retrospective 73 McKuen, Rod
Me and my shadow Grey, Joel see Billy Rose medley
Mean time Yarborough, Glenn
Medley #2 Alberghetti, Anna Maria
Medley - Osmond Brothers The Osmonds
Melting pot #2 Gaynor, Mitzi
Melting pot I Gaynor, Mitzi
Melting pot III Gaynor, Mitzi
Melting pot M.p. IV Gaynor, Mitzi
Melting pot part II Gaynor, Mitzi
Melting pot V Gaynor, Mitzi
Melting pot VI Gaynor, Mitzi
Memphis underground The Music Scene
Merry go-round Rubins, Paula
Michelle Eckstine, Billy
Mickey’s monkey The Music Scene
Midnight at the oasis Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
Mighty lak’ a rose Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Mimi Lane, Abbe see Celebrity medley
Miscellaneous cues The Late Liz
Miscellaneous cues MTM Emmy clips
Miscellaneous cues Never Steal Anything Wet
Miscellaneous cues Macho Callahan
Miscellaneous cues Three Girls Three
Miscellaneous cues Moonchild
Miscellaneous cues Lear TV film 1980, Norman
Miscellaneous cues TV Critics Awards 1977
Miscellaneous cues Randall, Tony
Miscellaneous cues MacLaine, Shirley
Miscellaneous cues Mr. Night
Miscellaneous TV cues Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Missing you Ladd, Cheryl
Mission - rock - bullwhip Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
Moja dro ga jacie kocham Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot VI
Money, money Grey, Joel see Cabaret
Mood indigo Rawls, Lou see Ellington medley (fix)
Moonlight and shadows Lamour, Dorothy see South Sea medley
Moonlight becomes you Crosby, Bing
Moonlight becomes you Lamour, Dorothy see South Sea medley
More than you know Grey, Joel see Billy Rose medley
Mountain greenery Ross, Diana see Rodgers and Hart medley
Mountain greenery The Supremes
Movies were movies Cavett, Dick
Movin’ on MacLaine, Shirley
Mr. Wonderful Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
Much higher than I Warwick, Dionne
Music and the mirror Reynolds, Debbie
Music Man - medley Jones, Shirley
The music that makes me dance Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
My Cherie The Music Scene
My favorite things Greco, Buddy
My favorite things ABC 25th anniversary
My favorite things Reese, Della
My friend the doctor Bushkin, Joe
My funny Valentine Ross, Diana see Rodgers and Hart medley
My funny Valentine Lucien, John
My kind of town Basie, Count
My kind of town Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
My melody of love Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot II
My melody of love Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot VI
My ship Reese, Della
My tailor is rich The Music Scene
My way Run America live tv ‘78
My wild Irish rose Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot V
My wild Irish rose Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot II
Nancy and Frank Jr. medley Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Nancy with the laughin’ face Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Nancy’s walk M.I.M. pilot
Nearness of you Damone, Vic
The need to be Eckstine, Billy
Neige sur liege McKuen, Rod
Never can say good-bye Falana, Lola
Never can say goodbye Lane, Abbe
Nevertheless Ann-Margret see Show biz medley
New world coming Elliot, [Mama] Cass see Cass’ golden oldies
New York, New York Newley, Anthony see Opening cont.
Newley overture ‘76 Newley, Anthony
Newley-Hamlisch overture Hamlisch, Marvin
Nice and easy Basie, Count
Night and day Rogers, Ginger
Night and day Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Night life Smith, Keely
A nightingale sang in Berkeley Square Martin Show, Tony see Travlin’ medley part I
No one will ever know Raney, Sue see Where does love go/No one will....
Nobody does it better Run America live tv ‘78
Nothing can stop me now! Reese, Della
A now and later love Lewis, Jerry
Nursery rhyme.... Gaynor, Mitzi
O du Lieber Augustin Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot IV
O sole mio Alberghetti, Anna Maria see Medley #2
O sole mio! Basie, Count
Oh look at me now Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Oh mama Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Oh what a beautiful morning Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy see Oklahoma medley
Oh what a night The Music Scene
Oklahoma - medley Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy
Oklahoma! Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy see Oklahoma medley
Ol’ man river Crosby, Bing
An old-fashioned wedding Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Oliver Twist McKuen, Rod see McKuen retrospective 73
On a wonderful day like today Hartman, David
On Broadway Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
On the apple tree Raney, Sue see Windmills of your mind-On the....
On the avenue Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
On the bandstand ABC 25th anniversary see Welk-Lennon Sisters medley
On top of old smokey Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Once in a lifetime Eckstine, Billy
Once was a time I thought Raney, Sue
One Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
One bad apple The Osmonds
One, closing bill board Baryshnikov on Broadway
One foot, other foot Rodgers/Hart tv special see Family of man medley
One of a kind Grey, Joel
One of a kind Minnelli, Liza
One piece at a time Andrews, Julie
One step Zadora, Pia
One to one b.g. #2 Andrews, Julie
One to one–opening Andrews, Julie
One.... —
One’s act enough Honey & Sis
Open for biz Raney, Sue
Opening Davis, Charles
Opening —